# **DIVYANGI MAHAJAN**

+91 7780989702 \$\divyangi.mahajan17@gmail.com



### **OBJECTIVE**

Versatile and tech enthusiast developer with over 5 years of leveraging experience in software engineering and implementing new technologies to maximize development efficiency. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reach-ability and security.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Kurukshetra University , Geeta Engineering College

Aug 2014 - May 2018 — Haryana, India

• Awarded with an honors degree for Bachelor's in technology, Computer Sciences.

### **SKILLS**

**Experienced** React JS, Javascript, Node JS, Redux, Typescript, Es6, HTML, CSS, CMS- Contentful.

Familiar Java, Scala, PostgreSQL, Oracle DB.

Soft Skills Time Management, Team Work, Problem Solving, Engaging Presentation.

#### EXPERIENCE

### Senior Software Engineer

Feb 2022 - Present

LTIMindtree – Delhi,IN

- Implemented Page Optimization techniques for web pages, Best Practices in Typescript and handled Cross Browser compatibility issues in web pages.
- Participated in bug thrashing sessions to discuss and resolve bugs with developers.
- Wrote jest test cases for testing UI components and also designed end to end test cases to mock the functionality.
- Implemented new website design layout for conversion of existing static websites to responsive.
- Collaborated with team on implementing new features and UX in an Agile environment.

## System Engineer Mar 2019 - Feb 2022

Tata Consultancy Services – Noida, IN

- Design and develop at all layers (front-end + back-end) public-facing applications.
- Primarily used React Js, Node JS, Javascript, Redux and PostgreSql database.
- Played major role in layout modifications to improve the functionality.

### Software Developer

Jun 2018 - Feb 2019

Skill Lotto Solutions – Gurugram, IN

- Developed and evolved consumer-facing, multi-channel roadmap for desktop, mobile and mobile web applications.
- Organize and handle bugs and issues reported from users, continuously update software to meet client needs.
- Developed the basis for application to be launched in new states of India

# Summer Intern

July 2016 - Aug 2016

Hewlett Packard - Noida, IN

- Successfully completed training in Core Java with Android.
- Scored B+ grade and developed a Quiz android application.

### CERTIFICATIONS

• Javascript by Hackerrank • Core Java with Android by Hewlett Packard • Advanced Java by Ducat